

CONTACT ME AT

- Navi Mumbai, Seawoods, MH,
- sarahundre12@gmail.com
- +91-85911 59512

SKILLS SUMMARY

- C++
- Java
- MySQL
- Python
- Al
- Android Application development

AWARDS RECEIVED

DEWA Conservation Award (2014 - 2015)

SCHOLARSHIP RECEIVED

- Guangdong Government
 Outstanding International
 Student Scholarship
- South China University of Technology International Scholarship for Excellence

VOLUNTEER

Volunteer Metro Staff at Guangzhou Metro Station during Canton Fair

Awareness campaign

Enviromental Programs

LANGUAGE

English (IELTS - 7.5)

Hindi

University level Intermediate Chinese

SARA SAJID UNDRE

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth: 12 Jan 2000

Ambitious student pursuing Computer Science and Technology degree. A team-oriented individual with an exemplary work ethic, highly organized, proactive and punctual. Interested in acquiring hands-on experience in order to enhance personal skills and knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Warehouse Associate

Amazon, Dubai, U.A.E | Oct 2018 - Jan 2019

- Inspected incoming and outgoing shipments to verify accuracy and prevent errors.
- Managed quality assurance program, including on-site evaluations, internal audits

Translator

Chinese software companies | Oct 2019 - Nov 2019

 Assisted with the translation of their application into Hindi and English.

Game Tester

Guangzhou, China | dec 2019

- Provided subjective feedback to shape game development by applying personal and third-party taste profiles.
- Followed procedural protocols for determining content functionality and quality
- Collaborated with team members to test multi-player content during quality assurance tasks

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

South China University of Technology, Guangzhou China B.E in Computer Science And Technology Jan 2019 - Current

The Central School (NIMS Group), Dubai UAE

High School Diploma | Aug 2008 - July 2018